<activities>
    <activity>
        <name>Poultry Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 27, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dairy Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Animals/Dairy Cattle/Showing</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <when>July 30, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dog Show</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <category>Animals/Dogs</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 6:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Horse Interview</name>
        <category>Animals/Horses</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sheep Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Animals/Sheep</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Cloverbud Stuffed Animal Show</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 1:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Crafting</name>
        <category>Learn with us Online</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <description>Pick up a craft kit at one of the library pickup
        locations (Dryden Southworth Library or Tompkins County Public
        Library at Green Street) and make the craft following the
        YouTube videos on this page.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Goat Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Animals/Goats/Showing</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <when>July 28, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Plant Science Activity</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <when>July 30, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
        <when>July 31, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dairy Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests/Study Materials</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Livestock Quiz Bowl</name>
        <category>Contests/Kahoots</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 30, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dairy Quiz Bowl</name>
        <category>Contests/Kahoots</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Consumer and Family Sciences Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests/Kahoots</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 27, 2021 2:00 PM EDT</when>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Plant Science Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests/Kahoots</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 28, 2021 1:00 PM EDT</when>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Laughing Goat Fiber Farm Tour</name>
        <category>Animals/Goats</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Vaccinations</name>
        <category>Animals/Alpacas</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Shearing</name>
        <category>Animals/Alpacas</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Alpaca Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <category>Animals/Alpacas</category>
        <when>July 28, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Giddy Goats Club</name>
        <category>Animals/Goats</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Rabbit Hopping</name>
        <category>Animals/Rabbits and Cavy</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <demonstration>There will be a live rabbit hopping
        demonstration at the Pole Barn.</demonstration>
        <when>July 31, 2021 12:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Showmanship</name>
        <category>Animals/Rabbits and Cavy</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Gallery</name>
        <category>Animals/Rabbits and Cavy</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Rabbit and Cavy Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <category>Animals/Rabbits and Cavy</category>
        <when>July 31, 2021 9:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Chicken Buses</name>
        <category>Animals/Poultry</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Gallery</name>
        <category>Animals/Poultry</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Stomach</name>
        <category>Animals/Dairy Cattle/Anatomy</category>
        <details>
        Dairy cattle are ruminants, meaning their stomach is divided into four compartments. 
        These compartments are often refered to as "stomachs".  The food travels through
        the stomachs in reverse alphabetical order, the rumen first, then the reticulum,
        followed by the omasum, and finally the abomasum.</details>
        <stomachs>
            <rumen>The rumen is the first stomach.  It is sometimes called the "fermentation vat",
            since it is the largest stomach in a cow's body (taking up 80%).  Microorgamisms in the
            rumen, bacteria, fungi, and protazoa, ferment grasses, breaking down the carbohydrates. 
            It also breaks down some protein.  The protein that gets broken down in the rumen is
            called rumen degradeable protien; the protein that passes through unchanged is called
            rumen undegradeable protein, or by-pass protein.  Volatile fatty acids are also produced
            in this stomach.  Acetic acid is used for energy and milkfat.  Butyric acid is an
            undesireable component of silage.  Propionic acid is the precursor to glucose. The
            rumen is not fully developed in a newborn calf.  It is important to give calves grain
            and hay to facilitate the development of the rumen.  Normally, a calf starts chewing its
            cud at 2-3 weeks of age, when the rumen is more fully developed.</rumen>
            <reticulum>The reticulum is also known as the honeycomb.  It is the stomach compartment nearest
            the heart.  Hardware disease occurs in this stomach.  Hardware disease happens when a cow
            swallows hardware.  To decrease the risk of the hardware piercing the wall of the reticulum
            and piercing the heart, cows are given magnets using a balling gun.  If the cow licks her
            nose after the magnet is given, it's likely that they have swallowed the magnet.</reticulum>
            <omasum>The omasum is the third stomach, sometimes called the manyplies, since its many
            folds look like the pages of a book.  The extra surface area provided by the folds helps
            the omasum to dehydrate food before it is passed on into the abomasum.</omasum>
            <abomasum>The abomasum is the fourth and final stomach.  Since it is the stomach closest
            to a human's stomach, it is also known as the true stomach.  It is the largest stomach
            at birth, taking up 25% of a calf's body.  The esophogeal groove diverts milk past the
            rumen, which is not fully developed yet, and into the abomasum.  The abomasum uses acid
            to break down proteins into amino acids, which will later be absorbed in the small
            intestine.</abomasum>
        </stomachs>
        <resources>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/files/2013/12/PDCAShowmanshipEvalCard.pdf</r>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/dairy-events/showing-dairy-cattle/</r>
            <r>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0145/8808/4272/files/A3725.pdf</r>
            <r>https://web.extension.illinois.edu/equiz/</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/dairy-youth-programs/quizbowl/dairy-quizbowl-study-questions/</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/2019-Junior-Dairy-Quiz-Bowl-Questions_final.pdf?fwd=no</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/2018-Junior-Dairy-Quizbowl-Questions-All-Rounds.pdf?fwd=no</r>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/files/2014/03/Dairy_Judging_Workbook.pdf</r>
            <r>http://www.uobabylon.edu.iq/eprints/publication_12_15838_806.pdf</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Herbs</name>
        <category>Horticulture/Food</category>
        <uses>...
        </uses>
        <benefits>...
        </benefits>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Flowers</name>
        <category>Horticulture</category>
        <uses>...
        </uses>
        <benefits>...
        </benefits>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Storytime</name>
        <category>Learn with us Online</category>
        <description>Each storytime is videotaped and can be shown on YouTube or played on this page.
        Storytimes will last about 20 minutes and will be divided into two parts. 
        4-H members will read a book about the fair or animals to an audience on Zoom.  Then, a 4-H
        member will guide an interactive sing-along, also about the fair or animals.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Patterns</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fiber Arts</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Gallery</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fiber Arts</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Patterns</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Hobby Crafts</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Gallery</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fine Arts</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Food Donation Project</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>The Botany Besties 4-H Club is committed to helping provide food security as
        our community service project.  Our food donation project was crafted by one of our
        club members, Greta Garrison. Her goal is to provide fresh food access through the
        Friendship Donation Network which provides fresh vegetables to underserved members
        of our community. Last summer each club member was encouraged to plant a row in
        their garden for donation. When planning your gardens this spring, we invite you to
        dedicate a small space, and place in your heart to this program.  For more information
        on how you can help, contact our project manager at stickandstonefarm@gmail.com, or
        visit:</summary>
        <r>Friendship Donation Network Food Hubs: https://friendshipdonations.org/hubs/</r>
        <r>Tompkins County Food Assistance Programs: http://ccetompkins.org/food/food-assistance-programs</r>
        <r>Tompkins County Healthy Food For All: http://ccetompkins.org/food/healthy-food-for-all</r>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Helping improve Food Security</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>According to the US Census, 16.9% of individuals in Tompkins County live at
        or below the poverty line and 30% of children qualify for school lunch programs.  In
        addition to the inability to pay for food, many individuals live in a food desert. 
        This means that the closest grocery store may be miles away, too far to walk, and
        public transportation is inconvenient or unaffordable to this population.  Vegetables
        do not keep well, and they need to be shopped for frequently in order to be fresh and
        have high nutritional value.  For the individuals who are at or below the poverty line,
        there are limited food choices.  Many are high in calories, but they are not always
        high in nutrition.  Obtaining high nutrition vegetables can be very expensive and
        inaccessible for this group.  I would like to create a comprehensive growing and education
        plan to address these issues.  Overall, I would like to build bridges between the many
        organizations helping to combat food insecurity in my community to create a stronger
        program with a continuum of education and support from the beginning to the end of the
        program.  Through word of mouth, support for each other, education, and collaboration,
        I hope for this program to become self-supporting, grow, and encourage others to help
        their communities.  This pilot program will serve as a model to extend to other
        communities.</summary>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vT82Wmo0-6Ceg82ksA8WTDON_oDG2Tlcy842W4Tb-WfkJueuUUB4nsLEwkgU2CPT1cGUzMZw6WH3G5T/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Cards to Thank Frontline Workers</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Mask Making</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <each-kit-includes>
            <e>5 pieces of fabric</e>
            <e>2 sewing needles</e>
            <e>1 spool of thread</e>
            <e>10 adjustable straps</e>
            <e>1 mask template</e>
            <e>1 stick of chalk</e>
        </each-kit-includes>
        <you-will-need>
            <y>A pair of fabric scissors or sharp all-purpose scissors.</y>
            <y>A computer to access Youtube.com.</y>
            <y>A sewing machine makes the process faster, however you may
            use the needles and thread included in the kit.</y>
            <y>An iron is helpful for making the material lay flat but is
            not essential.</y>
        </you-will-need>
        <instructions>
            <i>Start a stopwatch to keep track of your hours spent working
            on the project. Lay all of the materials out on a spacious
            surface.</i>
            <i>Navigate to YouTube.com and search the below tutorial:
            Make Fabric Face Mask at home | DIY Face Mask No Sewing Machine
            | Easy Face Mask Pattern by the channel Crafty Daily.  URL:
            https://tinyurl.com/1wwas5jq</i>
            <i>Watch and follow along with the video tutorial. Special notes:
            use the provided template instead of the dinner plate recommended
            in the video. Also, if you have a sewing machine use it in place
            of the needle and thread suggested in the video.</i>
            <i>IMPORTANT! Stop the video at 2:42 and search this new video
            into YouTube.com: It only takes 5 minutes to sew a simple mask
            | Face mask sewing tutorial | DIY face mask at home by the channel
            Mia. URL: http://tinyurl.com/v0nv2jrv  Please start this new video
            at 3:30, and continue watching until 4:25. This video will show you
            how to attach the adjustable straps not shown in the previous video.
            </i>
        </instructions>

    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Citizen Science Soil Project</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>We participated in a citizen science project run by the University
        of Oklahoma to take soil samples, which will be tested for new drugs.  We
        participated to give back to the community that did so much for us.</summary>
        <resources>
            <r>https://shareok.org/</r>
            <r>https://whatsinyourbackyard.org/</r>
        </resources>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTkBcqzz9c1hrdW7aLvuqktP_4AeKmHLHk6tnZPIK0Vnzy98QrAIGskIDYmPZirOYTCPKrb0G8kQCn3/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Bird Count with Cornell</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>Plenty of people turned to birdwatching during the past year,
        seeking enjoyment and relaxation. Chickadees, cardinals, finches and
        other birds are doing their part to lift human spirits.  The 24th annual
        Great Backyard Bird Count (GBBC), Feb. 12-15, is a great opportunity
        for budding birdwatchers and bird-count veterans to use their skills.
        People from around the world count the birds they see for at least 15
        minutes on one or more days of the count, and then enter their checklists
        online.  This helps to track the bird populations and migration routes.</summary>
        <resources>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/merlin-bird-id-app/</r>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/participate/</r>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/</r>
            <r>https://www.birds.cornell.edu/home</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>The activity at the October 2020 4-H Finger Lakes Conservation
        Club meeting was working with staff
        from the CSI (Community Science Institute) to do stream biomonitoring
        sampling following protocols similar to the Department of Environmental
        Conservation (DEC).  Members of the club learned about water quality
        and stream benthic macro invertebrates that live under the rocks in
        the stream. Water samples as well as organisms that were collected
        were taken and put into a data base to create a Biological Assessment
        profile to determine the biodiversity and health of the stream.</summary>
        <images>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling A</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling B</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling C</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling D</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling E</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling F</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling G</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling H</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling I</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kindness Rocks</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <description>Even during a pandemic, members of the Finger Lakes
        Conservation Club discovered "Kindness Rocks" and shared the idea
        with the Milk Duds/Jolly Ranchers 4-H club!  Below is a selection
        of the rocks members recently painted.  They will now leave these
        in the community for others to find.  One Kindness Rock was left
        by a member of the Finger Lakes Conservation Club at one of the blue
        food pantry.  The individual who found the rock posted a picture on
        Facebook saying how much they needed to hear the kind words that day.
        Help spread the kind words by making kindness rocks for your community
        as well!</description>
        <images>
            <image>Kindness Rocks A</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks B</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks C</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks D</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks E</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks F</image>

        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Beech Tree Celebrates Holidays with 4-H</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>The Botany Besties 4-H Club made origami poinsettias and
        snowflakes to donate to Beech Tree, a nearby long-term care facility. 
        40 origami poinsettias and 50 origami snowflakes were donated to
        brighten up the holidays for the residents of Beech Tree.  The patterns
        can be found in the YouTube videos below.</summary>
        <yt>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xcTjj2SEizw</yt>
        <yt>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aSWx128RgbE</yt>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>How to Make Scones</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'/Cooking Techniques</category>
        <category>Learn with us Online</category>
        <description>In the below video, the Sweets and Treats 4-H Club makes
        scones, raspberry, chocolate, and blueberry.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pDbINz0imOI"
                        title="YouTube video player of making scones with Sweets and Treats"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kitchen Gallery</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sausage Making</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'/Recipes</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Table Setting</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/A Meal's Best Friend</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Favorite Kitchen Tools</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/A Meal's Best Friend</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Veggie Art</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/Healthy Eating</category>
        <category>Live Event</category>
        <have-some-fun-with-your-veggies>We picked veggies from our garden and
        made art with them. You could make a person, a butterfly,or even a Mr.
        Potatohead! Afterwards, try to reuse the veggies.  This could be making
        an omlet, a salad, a pizza, or just eating them plain!  Don't worry,
        you don't need to cook the Mr. Potatohead. He's reusable veggie art! 
        Have some fun with your veggie art, and eat healthy!</have-some-fun-with-your-veggies>
        <where>This event will take place hands-on at the 4-H Acres.</where>
        <when>July 30, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Garden of Healthy Eatin'</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/Healthy Eating</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <description>This activity will take place at the 4-H Acres.  It
        will be presented by the Plant and Environmental Sciences Team
        (often abbreviated as P.E.S.T) all day.</description>
        <when>July 30, 2021 8:00 AM EDT</when>
        <when>July 31, 2021 8:00 AM EDT</when>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Bakeoff</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts</category>
        <summary>We know that there has been a lot of baking happening during the pandemic –
        it’s time to put on your apron, get out your favorite recipe and bake a delicious treat!
        The Holiday Bake off for Kids brings two important concepts together – positive youth
        development and baking! This contest is open to ALL youth 5 – 18 years of age. Youth
        work with an adult mentor to create an entry in one of the following categories: Cookies,
        Cakes, Breads, Decorated Items, Healthy Choices, and Candy.  The goal of the contest is to
        increase knowledge and appreciation of food around holiday celebrations, to build and
        strengthen the tradition of families baking together, to recognize skill and culinary
        arts talent, and to have FUN! So what are you waiting for, spend some quality time with
        your sons and daughters and whip up something delicious in the kitchen, they will
        learn to cherish this time with you. The “Best in Contest” will earn the giant Golden
        Spoon Award.  The Holiday Bake Off is held during National Baking Week in October at
        the Shops at Ithaca Mall.</summary>
        <images>
            <image>Bakeoff A</image>
            <image>Bakeoff B</image>
            <image>Bakeoff C</image>
            <image>Bakeoff D</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Photos</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'/Iron Chef</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Live Cooking</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'/Iron Chef</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <when>TBD</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fine Arts</name>
        <category>Gallery/Fair Projects</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>What do the ribbons mean?</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <html>
            <object data="data/What%20Do%20Ribbons%20Mean.pdf#toolbar=0&amp;navpanes=0&amp;scrollbar=0&amp;view=fitH"
                    type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="750px">
              <p>You don't have a PDF plugin, but you can download the file.</p>
              <a href="data/What%20Do%20Ribbons%20Mean.pdf">What Do the Ribbons Mean?</a>
            </object>
        </html>
        <text-version>Projects are graded against a set of criteria, not
        against other projects.  A blue ribbon means the project is
        excellent, and meets expectations.  Red ribbons mean good,
        projects meet most expectations.  White ribbons are given to projects
        that have met some expectations, but not all.  At the 4-H Fair,
        some projects are also given a marking called "Selected for State",
        meaning that they exceeded expectations and the 4-Her went above and beyond
        in creating the project.  The project will then go to be judged
        at the State Fair.</text-version>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Register Your Project</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <details>Please visit the below pages for the forms and information
        on registering your project for the Tompkins County 4-H Fair.</details>
        <resources>
            <r>http://ccetompkins.org/4-h-youth/activities-events/4-h-youth-fair</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/50924/Stationary_Exhibit_Registration.pdf?1620139270</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/50784/Fair_Book_Revised_2021.pdf?1619622561</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/45313/2020_Double_Entry_Card_Fillable.pdf?1591723416</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sample evaluation</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <description>Watch the following YouTube to see a sample fair
        project evaluation done between two 4-H members.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kxaF1RuspMY"
                        title="YouTube video player of a Sample 4-H Evaluation"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Awards</name>
        <category>Gallery</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fun at the Fair</name>
        <category>Gallery</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Winning Wednesday</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <html>...</html>
        <when>July 14, 2021</when>
        <when>July 21, 2021</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fall Festival at Tractor Supply</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Donations to Tompkins County 4-H</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Chicken BBQ</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <html>...</html>
    </activity>
</activities>
