<activities>
    <activity>
        <name>Kritter Kamp</name>
        <category>Animals</category>
        <description>Kritter Kamp is a program for youth between the ages
        of 9 and 13 who have an interest in learning more about farm animals
        (dairy, goats, sheep, dog and rabbits). Experienced 4-H teens mentor
        the campers as they learn about animal behavior and care, different
        breeds, anatomy, the importance of agriculture and farm animals in our
        society, and general safety with animals. They will be provided with
        an animal and the equipment needed for the care and preparation of
        the animal for show. The highlight will be a show experience Saturday
        afternoon. Participants will demonstrate what they have learned as they
        present their animal in the show ring.</description>
        <images>
            <image>Kritter Kamp A</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp B</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp C</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp D</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp E</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp F</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp G</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp H</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp I</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp J</image>
            <image>Kritter Kamp K</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Poultry Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 27, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dairy Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <description>Attend the Dairy Show and Showmanship competition.</description>
        <when>July 30, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Dog Show</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 6:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sheep Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Cloverbud Stuffed Animal Show</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 1:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Goat Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <description>Attend the Goat Show and Showmanship competition.</description>
        <when>July 28, 2021 10:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Plant Science Activity</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <description>The P.E.S.T will be holding a plant science activity.</description>
        <when>July 30, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
        <when>July 31, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kahoot Livestock Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 30, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
        <description>Test your knowledge of all livestock in
        this fun, online Kahoot!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kahoot Dairy Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 29, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
        <description>Test your knowledge of dairy
        sciences in this fun Kahoot for youth!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kahoot Consumer and Family Sciences Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 27, 2021 2:00 PM EDT</when>
        <description>Test your knowledge of family and consumer
        sciences like sewing and cooking in this fun Kahoot
        for youth!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kahoot Plant Science Challenge</name>
        <category>Contests</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 28, 2021 1:00 PM EDT</when>
        <description>Test your knowledge of plant
        sciences in this fun Kahoot for youth!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Laughing Goat Fiber Farm Tour</name>
        <category>Animals/Goats</category>
        <description>The Giddy Goats will make a tour of the Laughing Goat
        Fiber Farm.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Vaccinations</name>
        <category>Animals/Alpacas</category>
        <description>Alpacas are vaccinated to protect them from disease. 
        It's important to protect them from disease so they can produce
        wool and healthy crias (baby alpacas).</description>
        <types-of-vaccine>There are three types of vaccines:  Killed
        or toxoid, modified live, and recombinant.  With all of
        the vaccines, vaccinating a sick animal is not effective. 
        Animals should be vaccinated 2-3 weeks after recovering. 
        The vaccines also do not provide full protection, and
        efficacy of the vaccine is affected by many factors. 
        Antibodies found in colostrum, the mother's first milk,
        can interfere with some vaccines, so crias often require
        additional boosters.</types-of-vaccine>
        <killed-or-toxoid>Killed or toxoid vaccines contain
        the killed bacteria or virus, which means it is safe
        and the bacteria or virus is unable to reproduce. 
        This makes the killed or toxoid vaccines preferred for
        pregnant animals.  Killed vaccines do not always produce
        a strong immune response, so boosters are required 2-4
        weeks after the first shot and once a year every year
        after.</killed-or-toxoid>
        <modified-live>Modified live vaccines have some parts
        of the bacteria or virus that trigger the immune response. 
        This type of vaccine causes a mild infection,
        which increases the immune response and thus makes the
        vaccine last longer.  Vaccines are designed for use in
        a specific species, so they shouldn't be used in
        alpacas or anything else in the camelid family.</modified-live>
        <recombinant>Recombinant vaccines have a piece of the
        bacteria or virus, such as the spike protein causing the
        immune response.  The bacteria or virus is unable to
        reproduce, while still causing a strong immune response,
        thus making the vaccine last longer.</recombinant>
        <clostridial-vaccination>Alpacas and sheep need similar
        vaccines as sheep.  Twice a year, in the spring and autumn,
        alpacas are given a clostridial vaccination.  Crias can
        be vaccinated at 6-8 weeks and given a booster 4-6 weeks. 
        Then, crias are given another booster at 6 months of age
        and every year after.  If clostridial diseases have
        affected young animals on the farm, an extra vaccination
        can take place at 6-10 days of age for at-risk crias.</clostridial-vaccination>
        <clostridial-diseases>
            <c>Tetanus:  Poisoning from a neurotoxin caused by
            Clostridium tetani.  There are intermittent spasms
            of the muscles which can lead to death.</c>
            <c>Pulpy kidney/enterotoxemia:  Triggered when
            alpacas switch to feeds rich in starch, sugar,
            and/or protein.  High levels of these nutrients
            cause normally present Clostridium perfringens
            Type D bacteria undergo rapid growth in the small
            intestine.  As the bacteria increase in number,
            they release toxins causing damage to the small
            intestines, among other organs.  Alpacas will
            abruptly go off feed, become lethargic, show
            signs of stomach pain, have loose stool, lose
            the ability to stand (due to the toxin's effects
            on the brain), and die quickly with no previous
            signs of disease.</c>
            <c>Black leg:  Causes swelling of the muscles and
            necrotizing myositis in large muscles.  It's called
            black leg due to the color the muscles turn when
            animals are infected with the disease.  The muscles
            have a sweetish odor, small bubbles, dry and spongy,
            with little edema.  The tongue and diaphragm can
            also be affected.  Black leg can cause acute, severe
            lameness, marked depression, fever, focal hot and
            painful swelling, cold and insensitive skin, with
            decreased blood flow to affected areas.  Highly
            fatal.</c>
            <c>Black's disease/infectious necrotic hepatitis: 
            Caused by Clostridium novyi type B.  Death is sudden
            with little to no clinical signs, but is limited
            to alpacas also infected with liver flukes.  Lesions
            are grayish yellow, necrotic foci in diseased tissue. 
            The lesions are caused by young, migrating flukes,
            the host to the bacteria.</c>
            <c>Malignant edema:  Caused by severe, often fatal
            spread of bacterial toxins through the bloodstream. 
            Symptoms include loss of appetite, intoxication,
            and high fever, swelling around the site of infection.</c>
        </clostridial-diseases>
        <resources>
            <r>https://www.incaalpaca.co.uk/alpaca-info/about-alpacas/what-alpacas-need/</r>
            <r>https://www.midwestshearing.com/articles/vaccinations</r>
            <r>https://extension.colostate.edu/topic-areas/agriculture/enterotoxemia-overeating-disease-of-sheep-and-goats-8-018/</r>
            <r>https://criagenesis.cc/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CriaGenesis-Vacc-5-in-1a-1.pdf</r>
            <r></r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Alpaca Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 28, 2021 4:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Rabbit Hopping</name>
        <category>Animals/Rabbits and Cavy</category>
        <summary>Rabbit hopping was first introduced in the 1970s in
        Europe.  The rules are based on the rules of horse show jumping,
        modified to better suit rabbits.  There are several different types
        of courses to compete in.  The youth at 4-H assembled this video
        to demonstrate a straight course.</summary>
        <html>
            <p>For more information on rabbit hopping (or showjumping),
            take a look at this link:</p>
            <a href="https://yellowbrookrabbitry.com/all-about-rabbit-hopping-showjumping/"
            target="_blank">
                Yellow Brook Rabitry Rabbit Hopping</a>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%; padding-bottom: 10px;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/05NMBD8bqIU"
                        title="YouTube video player of rabbit hopping"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <when>July 31, 2021 12:00 PM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Rabbit and Cavy Show and Showmanship</name>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <when>July 31, 2021 9:00 AM EDT</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Chicken Buses</name>
        <category>Animals/Poultry</category>
        <description>Some chickens live in old school buses.  These buses
        provide protection from predators and the elements.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Poultry Gallery</name>
        <category>Animals/Poultry</category>
        <description>Send in pictures of your chickens!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Stomach</name>
        <category>Animals/Dairy Cattle/Anatomy</category>
        <details>
        Dairy cattle are ruminants, meaning their stomach is divided into four compartments. 
        These compartments are often refered to as "stomachs".  The food travels through
        the stomachs in reverse alphabetical order, the rumen first, then the reticulum,
        followed by the omasum, and finally the abomasum.</details>
        <stomachs>
            <rumen>The rumen is the first stomach.  It is sometimes called the "fermentation vat",
            since it is the largest stomach in a cow's body (taking up 80%).  Microorgamisms in the
            rumen, bacteria, fungi, and protazoa, ferment grasses, breaking down the carbohydrates. 
            It also breaks down some protein.  The protein that gets broken down in the rumen is
            called rumen degradeable protien; the protein that passes through unchanged is called
            rumen undegradeable protein, or by-pass protein.  Volatile fatty acids are also produced
            in this stomach.  Acetic acid is used for energy and milkfat.  Butyric acid is an
            undesireable component of silage.  Propionic acid is the precursor to glucose. The
            rumen is not fully developed in a newborn calf.  It is important to give calves grain
            and hay to facilitate the development of the rumen.  Normally, a calf starts chewing its
            cud at 2-3 weeks of age, when the rumen is more fully developed.</rumen>
            <reticulum>The reticulum is also known as the honeycomb.  It is the stomach compartment nearest
            the heart.  Hardware disease occurs in this stomach.  Hardware disease happens when a cow
            swallows hardware.  To decrease the risk of the hardware piercing the wall of the reticulum
            and piercing the heart, cows are given magnets using a balling gun.  If the cow licks her
            nose after the magnet is given, it's likely that they have swallowed the magnet.</reticulum>
            <omasum>The omasum is the third stomach, sometimes called the manyplies, since its many
            folds look like the pages of a book.  The extra surface area provided by the folds helps
            the omasum to dehydrate food before it is passed on into the abomasum.</omasum>
            <abomasum>The abomasum is the fourth and final stomach.  Since it is the stomach closest
            to a human's stomach, it is also known as the true stomach.  It is the largest stomach
            at birth, taking up 25% of a calf's body.  The esophogeal groove diverts milk past the
            rumen, which is not fully developed yet, and into the abomasum.  The abomasum uses acid
            to break down proteins into amino acids, which will later be absorbed in the small
            intestine.</abomasum>
        </stomachs>
        <quiz>
            <html>
                <h4>Click on the question below to reveal some choices.  Select whichever
                one you think is correct to test your knowledge!</h4>
                <button class="slide-down-btn">
                    Which stomach compartment is responsible for fermentation?
                </button>
                <div class="slide-down">
                    <ul class="choices">
                        <li><button value="incorrect" onclick="quiz(this)" style="font-size:1.15em;">Abomasum</button></li>
                        <li><button value="correct" onclick="quiz(this)" style="font-size:1.15em;">Rumen</button></li>
                        <li><button value="incorrect" onclick="quiz(this)" style="font-size:1.15em;">Omasum</button></li>
                        <li><button value="incorrect" onclick="quiz(this)" style="font-size:1.15em;">Reticulum</button></li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
            </html>
        </quiz>
        <resources>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/files/2013/12/PDCAShowmanshipEvalCard.pdf</r>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/dairy-events/showing-dairy-cattle/</r>
            <r>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0145/8808/4272/files/A3725.pdf</r>
            <r>https://web.extension.illinois.edu/equiz/</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/dairy-youth-programs/quizbowl/dairy-quizbowl-study-questions/</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/2019-Junior-Dairy-Quiz-Bowl-Questions_final.pdf?fwd=no</r>
            <r>https://dairy.ces.ncsu.edu/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/2018-Junior-Dairy-Quizbowl-Questions-All-Rounds.pdf?fwd=no</r>
            <r>https://fyi.extension.wisc.edu/dairyyouth/files/2014/03/Dairy_Judging_Workbook.pdf</r>
            <r>http://www.uobabylon.edu.iq/eprints/publication_12_15838_806.pdf</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Storytime</name>
        <category>Learn with us Online</category>
        <description>Each storytime is videotaped and can be shown on YouTube or played on this page.
        4-H members will read a book about the fair or animals in the video.  These
        videos were created by kids for kids.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BA6F1lNfcXI"
                        title="YouTube video player of Storytime"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fiber Arts Gallery</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fiber Arts</category>
        <description>More photos coming soon...help by sending in some of your
        fiber arts photos!</description>
        <images>
            <image>Pom Pom Animals</image>
            <image>Fiber Arts B</image>
            <image>Fiber Arts C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Patterns</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Hobby Crafts</category>
        <description>Follow along with these patterns to make a project.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%; padding-bottom: 10px;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z0-mlZvJD-E"
                        title="YouTube video player of Origami Fireworks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sOE863z3eD8"
                        title="YouTube video player of Universe Kusudama"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/74CVSdRRdp0"
                        title="YouTube video player of Bargello Interlocking Crochet"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Hobby Crafts Gallery</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Hobby Crafts</category>
        <description>Feel free to send in your hobby craft photos.</description>
        <images>
            <image>Pom Pom Animals</image>
            <image>Fuse Beads</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fine Arts Gallery</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fine Arts</category>
        <description>Send your pictures of Fine Arts projects in to
        have them displayed here!</description>
        <images>
            <image>Fine Arts A</image>
            <image>Fine Arts B</image>
            <image>Fine Arts C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Earring Making</name>
        <category>Arts and Crafts/Fine Arts</category>
        <description>At a F.L.O.W. club meeting, one of the members led an activity
        on earring making.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Plants and Animals</category>
        <name>Mimicry and Look-a-likes</name>
        <details>Evolutionary Mimicry is a term for when one species evolves
        to mimic another.  The Bee Orchid evolved to mimic a female Orchid Bee.
        It not only looks like a female Orchid Bee, it also releases pheromones,
        a sort of smelly substance, to attract the male Orchid Bees.</details>
        <question>How does this help the Bee Orchid?</question>
        <answer>For the Bee Orchid, it increases the survival rate because it
        is able to spread more of its pollen.</answer>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vRfUgtlTIMu-HfBoe48vtIScRalyZxQQM3XCk8L4E5bbqJkKDB2gJpmTaSYh2EtbpTXrw2DD-nqU_2x/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Growing Plants</category>
        <name>All Cooped Up</name>
        <details>How can we grow salads indoors?</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSqDIK3EUFaYaUxxVhX41b9xjJEZqxbf4IUdPNiW3SwBwkULc3CjaEk5wBeCxSi68iVC95IH2GxHawM/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Plants and Animals</category>
        <name>Buggy Day</name>
        <details>What insects are beneficial, and which are considered pests?  For more details,
        open the speaker notes by clicking on the three dots to the right of the arrows
        on the bottom of the slideshow.  Then, choose "Open speaker notes".</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQlHelDz5HiJmOOO9uUX46NMuJrIGd9r3wBEypm1LK77BPWTXb_EAnDUok9lkB1p4OeX2GnOyM0aZO9/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/How Plants Work</category>
        <name>Hidden Colors</name>
        <details>Chromatography is the process of seperating out molecules based
        on their polarities.</details>
        <question>Could this still be done in space?</question>
        <answer>Since the capillary action that drives the molecules is not
        gravity dependant, Chromatography done in space would look similar to
        Chromatography done on Earth.</answer>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSAKvSbRRGsQQNbJL6wELRdeO0iAnkHx47H1zCNSh_j6W-45EkzHrnaGxTEPiOCeGnAqfwVNVFdYzot/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/How Plants Work</category>
        <name>Mysteries of Color</name>
        <details>How do we see?  How do plants see?  And how can we use this to help
        plants grow?</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTLrZ0YRXKfVJk2Em9yv3s_Sgj-mZgA2qNI7EBummsSZZZKBA08596og6TcUrbEbnTwZ9X02KzY94U_/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
            <p>To experiment more with how color filters work, feel free to experiment
            with this website:</p>
            <a href="https://phet.colorado.edu/sims/html/color-vision/latest/color-vision_en.html">
            Color Vision</a>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture</category>
        <name>Top 5 Trees</name>
        <details>What are you five favorite trees?  One of our members shared theirs, along with information on how to
        identify each of them, how they are used, and where they grow.</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vT2Jra6FeXqZAGaGI8qDdsQ80pQRw4VPgps9hSgW4ZebgViHFnIJsdb_P_13NmLly66X3ylQ2w8IvP6/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/How Plants Work</category>
        <name>Soil pH</name>
        <details>Soil pH is very important for plants. For more details,
        open the speaker notes by clicking on the three dots to the right of the arrows
        on the bottom of the slideshow.  Then, choose "Open speaker notes".</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSvLB9QtATJTS1x-7UeHJlZ5eCm6-nYbU8CCty2J-z3AejcRv3IL19yPbsS0cvwX0Yj7xte5ljaDX_6/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OMXMlWybv8A"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <images>
            <image>Soil pH A</image>
            <image>Soil pH B</image>
            <image>Soil pH C</image>
            <image>Soil pH D</image>
            <image>Soil pH E</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Growing Plants</category>
        <name>Plant Propagation</name>
        <details>How can we make more plants?  We can propagate them.  For more details,
        open the speaker notes by clicking on the three dots to the right of the arrows
        on the bottom of the slideshow.  Then, choose "Open speaker notes".</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSVNm0VF0goDYQYFE8SzQmoiARptixSxzkylogsKTZfUTBBtR04J7pFtRhfPpZeg9H43garSz-alLDi/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Growing Plants</category>
        <name>Green Roofs</name>
        <details>The Botany Besties plan on making modular boxes to create a green roof at the 4-H Acres. 
        For more details, open the speaker notes by clicking on the three dots to the
        right of the arrows on the bottom of the slideshow.  Then, choose "Open speaker
        notes".</details>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTaxYklYLaTD_Eirh8uyZgxlqa6EArOlLvJlekUqTK0HVjF_YaNOOVuj7WrCjYoEveIP2kjyYJzNT_G/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <category>Horticulture/Plants and Animals</category>
        <name>Pollinator Taboo Game</name>
        <summary>Not only bees pollinate gardens!  Check out some other pollinators in the slideshow below.</summary>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSCPzXg1wPy_3FGkNbnTyoLvCKBlyiny7Yl2JhBPKWN0XFi2CP-3J3Y8WA2ZI0kvByV2WXMbruDQomx/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true"></iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Food Donation Project</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>The Botany Besties 4-H Club is committed to helping provide food security as
        our community service project.  Our food donation project was crafted by one of our
        club members, Greta Garrison. Her goal is to provide fresh food access through the
        Friendship Donation Network which provides fresh vegetables to underserved members
        of our community. Last summer each club member was encouraged to plant a row in
        their garden for donation. When planning your gardens this spring, we invite you to
        dedicate a small space, and place in your heart to this program.  For more information
        on how you can help, contact our project manager at stickandstonefarm@gmail.com, or
        visit:</summary>
        <r>Friendship Donation Network Food Hubs: https://friendshipdonations.org/hubs/</r>
        <r>Tompkins County Food Assistance Programs: http://ccetompkins.org/food/food-assistance-programs</r>
        <r>Tompkins County Healthy Food For All: http://ccetompkins.org/food/healthy-food-for-all</r>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Crafting</name>
        <category>Learn with us Online</category>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <description>Pick up a craft kit at one of the library pickup
        locations (Dryden Southworth Library or Tompkins County Public
        Library at Green Street) and make the craft following the
        YouTube videos on this page.  With the kits, we hope for kids
        to have a safe way to experience some of the activities held
        at the 4-H Fair while helping to develop a love for reading. 
        These crafting sessions were created by kids for kids.  We
        hope you enjoy!
        </description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%; padding-bottom: 10px;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Bi7F03XSc2A"
                        title="YouTube video player of making Animal Bookmarks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/A-XnIL-ZW1M"
                        title="YouTube video player of making Chenille Stem Critters"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Uy35aPc5LT8"
                        title="YouTube video player of making Spinners"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div>
                <br></br>
                <button class="form-btn slide-down-btn">Click here to give feedback on the Take and Make Craft Kits</button>
                <div class="slide-down">
                    <form action="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSev0bLWuSD3r4TxhDgGtXM8nZlR-4FdBs3qddnTCloE-w2Ihg/formResponse" method="post">
                        <textarea id="name-take-make" name="entry.1437279743" placeholder="Name" required="required" maxlength="200" rows="2"></textarea>
                        <textarea id="age-take-make" name="entry.2033389245" placeholder="Age of child" required="required" maxlength="200" rows="10"></textarea>
                        <textarea id="ease-take-make" name="entry.1907777736" placeholder="Ease of craft" required="required" maxlength="1000" rows="10"></textarea>
                        <textarea id="suggest-take-make" name="entry.143964855" placeholder="Suggestions on how to improve the kits" required="required" maxlength="1000" rows="10"></textarea>
                        <textarea id="suggest-take-make" name="entry.11063362" placeholder="Additional comments" required="required" maxlength="1000" rows="10"></textarea>
                        <br></br>
                        <input type="submit" value="Send"></input>
                    </form>
                </div>
            </div>
        </html>
        <images>
            <image>Crafting A</image>
            <image>Crafting B</image>
            <image>Crafting C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Helping improve Food Security</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>According to the US Census, 16.9% of individuals in Tompkins County live at
        or below the poverty line and 30% of children qualify for school lunch programs.  In
        addition to the inability to pay for food, many individuals live in a food desert. 
        This means that the closest grocery store may be miles away, too far to walk, and
        public transportation is inconvenient or unaffordable to this population.  Vegetables
        do not keep well, and they need to be shopped for frequently in order to be fresh and
        have high nutritional value.  For the individuals who are at or below the poverty line,
        there are limited food choices.  Many are high in calories, but they are not always
        high in nutrition.  Obtaining high nutrition vegetables can be very expensive and
        inaccessible for this group.  I would like to create a comprehensive growing and education
        plan to address these issues.  Overall, I would like to build bridges between the many
        organizations helping to combat food insecurity in my community to create a stronger
        program with a continuum of education and support from the beginning to the end of the
        program.  Through word of mouth, support for each other, education, and collaboration,
        I hope for this program to become self-supporting, grow, and encourage others to help
        their communities.  This pilot program will serve as a model to extend to other
        communities.</summary>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vT82Wmo0-6Ceg82ksA8WTDON_oDG2Tlcy842W4Tb-WfkJueuUUB4nsLEwkgU2CPT1cGUzMZw6WH3G5T/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Cards to Thank Frontline Workers</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <description>The Botany Besties 4-H club made cards to thank frontline workers. 
        They told about people they knew who were frontline workers while making their
        cards.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Mask Making</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <each-kit-includes>
            <e>5 pieces of fabric</e>
            <e>2 sewing needles</e>
            <e>1 spool of thread</e>
            <e>10 adjustable straps</e>
            <e>1 mask template</e>
            <e>1 stick of chalk</e>
        </each-kit-includes>
        <you-will-need>
            <y>A pair of fabric scissors or sharp all-purpose scissors.</y>
            <y>A computer to access Youtube.com.</y>
            <y>A sewing machine makes the process faster, however you may
            use the needles and thread included in the kit.</y>
            <y>An iron is helpful for making the material lay flat but is
            not essential.</y>
        </you-will-need>
        <instructions>
            <i>Start a stopwatch to keep track of your hours spent working
            on the project. Lay all of the materials out on a spacious
            surface.</i>
            <i>Navigate to the first YouTube video below or search the below tutorial:
            Make Fabric Face Mask at home | DIY Face Mask No Sewing Machine
            | Easy Face Mask Pattern by the channel Crafty Daily.  URL:
            https://tinyurl.com/1wwas5jq</i>
            <i>Watch and follow along with the video tutorial. Special notes:
            use the provided template instead of the dinner plate recommended
            in the video. Also, if you have a sewing machine use it in place
            of the needle and thread suggested in the video.</i>
            <i>IMPORTANT! Stop the video at 2:42 and search this new video
            into YouTube.com or watch the second YouTube Video: It only takes
            5 minutes to sew a simple mask
            | Face mask sewing tutorial | DIY face mask at home by the channel
            Mia. URL: http://tinyurl.com/v0nv2jrv  Please start this new video
            at 3:30, and continue watching until 4:25. This video will show you
            how to attach the adjustable straps not shown in the previous video.
            </i>
        </instructions>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%; padding-bottom: 10px;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uRfhuRNua_E"
                        title="YouTube video player of making masks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eOcWQufOx7A"
                        title="YouTube video player of making masks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Citizen Science Soil Project</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>We participated in a citizen science project run by the University
        of Oklahoma to take soil samples, which will be tested for new drugs.  We
        participated to give back to the community that did so much for us.</summary>
        <resources>
            <r>https://shareok.org/</r>
            <r>https://whatsinyourbackyard.org/</r>
        </resources>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vTkBcqzz9c1hrdW7aLvuqktP_4AeKmHLHk6tnZPIK0Vnzy98QrAIGskIDYmPZirOYTCPKrb0G8kQCn3/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Bird Count with Cornell</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>Plenty of people turned to birdwatching during the past year,
        seeking enjoyment and relaxation. Chickadees, cardinals, finches and
        other birds are doing their part to lift human spirits.  The 24th annual
        Great Backyard Bird Count (GBBC), Feb. 12-15, is a great opportunity
        for budding birdwatchers and bird-count veterans to use their skills.
        People from around the world count the birds they see for at least 15
        minutes on one or more days of the count, and then enter their checklists
        online.  This helps to track the bird populations and migration routes.</summary>
        <resources>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/merlin-bird-id-app/</r>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/participate/</r>
            <r>https://www.birdcount.org/</r>
            <r>https://www.birds.cornell.edu/home</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling</name>
        <category>Community Service/Citizen Science</category>
        <summary>The activity at the October 2020 4-H Finger Lakes Conservation
        Club meeting was working with staff
        from the CSI (Community Science Institute) to do stream biomonitoring
        sampling following protocols similar to the Department of Environmental
        Conservation (DEC).  Members of the club learned about water quality
        and stream benthic macro invertebrates that live under the rocks in
        the stream. Water samples as well as organisms that were collected
        were taken and put into a data base to create a Biological Assessment
        profile to determine the biodiversity and health of the stream.</summary>
        <results>Adrinna Hirtler from the CSI reported on the results of the stream
        biomonitoring:  A few weeks ago some hardy volunteers and I finished sorting
        and identifying the 2020 benthic macroinvertebrate biomonitoring samples. 
        I'm attaching a pdf showing the results for all 21 sites (in 12 different
        creeks) that were sampled. You can find more details about what the results
        mean on the CSI website (http://www.communityscience.org/bmi-results/) but
        to understand them at a quick glance, the number in the column on the right
        (Biological Assessment Profile or BAP) gives you an overall assessment of
        water quality at each site. The Cascadilla Creek downtown site curiously
        improved compared with recent years, though there are still quite a number
        of sites showing slight impacts. These results are now part of what's
        becoming a very nice long-term data set for many creeks in our area. 
        Congratulations to all of the wonderful volunteers who have contributed
        over the years and who continue to contribute today. Thanks especially to
        Paul Allderige who came into the lab almost every week this winter for
        Thursday open lab nights to help work through all of the samples. We
        were limited by the number of people allowed in the lab at once due to
        the pandemic, but none of the volunteers who came to help (we sincerely
        appreciate you ALL) were limited in their energy, keen observations and
        enthusiasm. Thanks again for a fun and productive sample sorting season!
        </results>
        <html>
            <object data="data/CSI-2020%20BMI%20RESULTS.pdf#toolbar=0&amp;navpanes=0&amp;scrollbar=0&amp;view=fitH"
                    type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="750px">
              <p>You don't have a PDF plugin, but you can download the file.</p>
              <a href="data/CSI-2020%20BMI%20RESULTS.pdf">Stream Biomonitoring Results</a>
            </object>
        </html>
        <images>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling A</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling B</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling C</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling D</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling E</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling F</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling G</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling H</image>
            <image>Stream Biomonitoring Sampling I</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kindness Rocks</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <description>Even during a pandemic, members of the Finger Lakes
        Conservation Club discovered "Kindness Rocks" and shared the idea
        with the Milk Duds/Jolly Ranchers 4-H club!  Below is a selection
        of the rocks members recently painted.  They will now leave these
        in the community for others to find.  One Kindness Rock was left
        by a member of the Finger Lakes Conservation Club at one of the blue
        food pantry.  The individual who found the rock posted a picture on
        Facebook saying how much they needed to hear the kind words that day.
        Help spread the kind words by making kindness rocks for your community
        as well!  Two cloverbuds also made videos describing the kindness rocks (or
        peace rocks) they made with their club, the Milk Duds.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tpxnj_q-p_g"
                        title="YouTube video player of Kindness Rocks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DL7-wT_4u50"
                        title="YouTube video player of Kindness Rocks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3sYhdMugveA"
                        title="YouTube video player of Kindness Rocks"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <images>
            <image>Kindness Rocks A</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks B</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks C</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks D</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks E</image>
            <image>Kindness Rocks F</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Beech Tree Celebrates Holidays with 4-H</name>
        <category>Community Service/Helping our Community</category>
        <summary>The Botany Besties 4-H Club made origami poinsettias and
        snowflakes to donate to Beech Tree, a nearby long-term care facility. 
        40 origami poinsettias and 50 origami snowflakes were donated to
        brighten up the holidays for the residents of Beech Tree.  The patterns
        can be found in the YouTube videos below.</summary>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xcTjj2SEizw"
                        title="YouTube video player of Snowflakes"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aSWx128RgbE"
                        title="YouTube video player of Poinsettias"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Favorite Kitchen Tools</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts</category>
        <description>What are your favorite kitchen tools?  Submit your tool,
        a picture, and a short description of why you like it.</description>
        <pastry-cutter>My favorite tool is the pastry cutter because I love making
        pie crust and it helps me cut the butter in faster.  Since it's metal, it
        stays cold and doesn't melt the butter, which makes the pie crust flakier.
        </pastry-cutter>
        <biscuit-cutter>My mom used this biscuit cutter when she was a kid.  It wasn't
        used a whole lot, so we're trying to make up for that now.  The scalloped
        edges turn brown and crispy, and every time I bite into a biscuit we cooked
        with this pastry cutter, I think of my mom and grammy.</biscuit-cutter>
        <whisk>Whisks are super cool!  If you whisk fast enough, you can make
        fluffed egg whites for marangues.  You can use them when making homemade
        gravy to keep lumps from forming (this is mainly what I use the whisk for;
        my gravy is generally lumpy).  They also combine your eggs and sugar into brownies. 
        Yum!  Thank you, whisk!</whisk>
        <images>
            <image>Pastry Cutter</image>
            <image>Biscuit Cutter</image>
            <image>Whisk</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>How to Make Scones</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'</category>
        <category>Learn with us Online/Cooking</category>
        <description>In the below video, the Sweets and Treats 4-H Club makes
        scones, raspberry, chocolate, and blueberry.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pDbINz0imOI"
                        title="YouTube video player of making scones with Sweets and Treats"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <recipe>
            <ingredients>
                <ingredient>2 cups flour</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/4 cup sugar</ingredient>
                <ingredient>2 tsp baking powder</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/4 tsp salt</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/2 cup (1 stick) very cold butter</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/2 cup heavy cream</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/4 tsp vanilla extract</ingredient>
                <ingredient>1/2 cup of either:  Rasberries, chocolate chips, or blueberries</ingredient>
                <ingredient>2 tbsp sugar</ingredient>
            </ingredients>
            <directions>
                <direction>Preheat oven to 375F.</direction>
                <direction>In a bowl, whisk together flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt.</direction>
                <direction>Cut the butter into tablespoon sized pieces, and using your hands,
                mix it into the flour until the flour and butter are indistinguishable.</direction>
                <direction>Whisk the heavy cream and vanilla together.</direction>
                <direction>Pour half of the heavy cream and vanilla mixture over the dough
                and sprinkle on half the sugar.</direction>
                <direction>Put dough on floured surface.</direction>
                <direction>Add your choice of add ins and gently work them into the dough by folding it
                in half and then flattening five times.</direction>
                <direction>Make a six inch round circle fo your dough about an inch thick and cut into wedges. 
                Place the wedges on a lined baking sheet.</direction>
                <direction>Pour on remaining heavy cream and vanilla mixture and sprinkle on remaining sugar.</direction>
                <direction>Bake 14-16 minutes or until golden brown.  Cool and enjoy!</direction>
            </directions>
        </recipe>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Kitchen Gallery</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'</category>
        <description>Help us by sending in pictures of what you're cooking!</description>
        <images>
            <image>Shortbread Cookies</image>
            <image>Omlet in a Bowl</image>
            <image>Borsch with Russian Blackbread</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sausage Making</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'</category>
        <description>The Milk Duds and Jolly Ranchers 4-H Club made sausages
        together as a club activity.  Try these recipes at home!</description>
        <polish-sausage>
            <p>18g kosher salt</p>
            <p>25g fresh garlic (chopped in food processor or mini chopper)</p>
            <p>1.3g dried marjoram</p>
            <p>4.4g black pepper</p>
            <p>1.3g dried marjoram</p>
        </polish-sausage>
        <italian-sausage>
            <p>18g kosher salt</p>
            <p>12g sugar</p>
            <p>7.8g fennel seed</p>
            <p>4g coriander</p>
            <p>1.6g red pepper flakes</p>
            <p>2.8g black pepper</p>
            <p>5.7g fresh garlic (chopped in food processor or mini-chopper)</p>
            <p>1.2g dried basil</p>
            <p>1.2g dried oregano</p>
            <p>9.4g paprika</p>
            <p>When mixing add 3 tbsp red wine vinegar per kg sausage</p>
        </italian-sausage>
        <bratwurst>
            <p>18g kosher salt</p>
            <p>2.6g black pepper</p>
            <p>2.2g ground dried ginger</p>
            <p>2.2g nutmeg</p>
            <p>3 tbsp dried milk (optional)</p>
            <p>When mixing add 1 egg and 1/2 cup ice cold heavy cream per kg sausage</p>
        </bratwurst>
        <tips>
            <tip>Keep your pork and liquids as cold as possible when
            mixing to prevent fat smearing.</tip>
            <tip>After mixing, make and cook a small patty to test
            flavor before stuffing or packaging.</tip>
            <tip>Be precise on salt measurements.</tip>
            <tip>Make sure your scales are tared to zero before
            measuring.</tip>
            <tip>Make sure the scales are measured in g or kg.</tip>
            <tip>Add a quarter cup of water to the meat when
            grinding to achieve a finer grind.</tip>
        </tips>
        <images>
            <image>Sausage Making A</image>
            <image>Sausage Making B</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Table Setting</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts</category>
        <description>A meal's no good if there's nowhere to put it...share
        pictures of your table setting as well!</description>
        <images>
            <image>Table Setting A</image>
            <image>Table Setting B</image>
            <image>Table Setting C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Veggie Art</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/Healthy Eating</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <have-some-fun-with-your-veggies>We picked veggies from our garden and
        made art with them. You could make a person, a butterfly,or even a Mr.
        Potatohead! Afterwards, try to reuse the veggies.  This could be making
        an omlet, a salad, a pizza, or just eating them plain!  Don't worry,
        you don't need to cook the Mr. Potatohead. He's reusable veggie art! 
        Have some fun with your veggie art, and eat healthy!</have-some-fun-with-your-veggies>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vQ44ZJwTM4y9laQa2K6VTzD5klOw5Ga-U1vGLphi_RVfWMUWjV3SMzpWw6uZaBxzEFUTX4V81VCiQzz/embed?delayms=3000"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <when>July 30, 2021 11:00 AM EDT</when>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Garden of Healthy Eatin'</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/Healthy Eating</category>
        <category>Live Events</category>
        <description>This activity will take place at the 4-H Acres.  It
        will be presented by the Plant and Environmental Sciences Team
        (often abbreviated as P.E.S.T) all day.</description>
        <when>July 30, 2021 8:00 AM EDT</when>
        <when>July 31, 2021 8:00 AM EDT</when>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Bakeoff</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts</category>
        <summary>We know that there has been a lot of baking happening during the pandemic 
        its time to put on your apron, get out your favorite recipe and bake a delicious treat!
        The Holiday Bake off for Kids brings two important concepts together  positive youth
        development and baking! This contest is open to ALL youth 5  18 years of age. Youth
        work with an adult mentor to create an entry in one of the following categories: Cookies,
        Cakes, Breads, Decorated Items, Healthy Choices, and Candy.  The goal of the contest is to
        increase knowledge and appreciation of food around holiday celebrations, to build and
        strengthen the tradition of families baking together, to recognize skill and culinary
        arts talent, and to have FUN! So what are you waiting for, spend some quality time with
        your sons and daughters and whip up something delicious in the kitchen, they will
        learn to cherish this time with you. The Best in Contest will earn the giant Golden
        Spoon Award.  The Holiday Bake Off is held during National Baking Week in October at
        the Shops at Ithaca Mall.</summary>
        <images>
            <image>Bakeoff A</image>
            <image>Bakeoff B</image>
            <image>Bakeoff C</image>
            <image>Bakeoff D</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Iron Chef</name>
        <category>Culinary Arts/What's Cookin'</category>
        <description>Teams of 3-4 kids make a meal in an hour using two secret
        ingredients.  In the past, apple cobbler, apple and chipotle, and spaghetti
        have won the competition.</description>
        <images>
            <image>Iron Chef A</image>
            <image>Iron Chef B</image>
            <image>Iron Chef C</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fair Projects</name>
        <category>Gallery</category>
        <description>Send us pictures of your fair projects this year.</description>
        <images>
            <image>Fairy Garden Alina</image>
            <image>Creative Cake Decorating Evaluation</image>
            <image>Educational Poster Evaluation</image>
            <image>Fine Arts Evaluation</image>
            <image>Food Evaluations</image>
            <image>Geranium Evaluation</image>
            <image>Plant Science Evaluation</image>
            <image>Record Book Evaluation</image>
            <image>Strawberry Cupcakes Evaluation 1</image>
            <image>Strawberry Cupcakes Evaluation 2</image>
            <image>Strawberry Cupcakes Evaluation 3</image>
            <image>Volunteer Registration</image>
            <image>Evelyn Plant Science</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>What do the ribbons mean?</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <html>
            <object data="data/What%20Do%20Ribbons%20Mean.pdf#toolbar=0&amp;navpanes=0&amp;scrollbar=0&amp;view=fitH"
                    type="application/pdf" width="100%" height="750px">
              <p>You don't have a PDF plugin, but you can download the file.</p>
              <a href="data/What%20Do%20Ribbons%20Mean.pdf">What Do the Ribbons Mean?</a>
            </object>
        </html>
        <text-version>Projects are graded against a set of criteria, not
        against other projects.  A blue ribbon means the project is
        excellent, and meets expectations.  Red ribbons mean good,
        projects meet most expectations.  White ribbons are given to projects
        that have met some expectations, but not all.  At the 4-H Fair,
        some projects are also given a marking called "Selected for State",
        meaning that they exceeded expectations and the 4-Her went above and beyond
        in creating the project.  The project will then go to be judged
        at the State Fair.</text-version>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Register Your Project</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <details>Please visit the below pages for the forms and information
        on registering your project for the Tompkins County 4-H Fair.</details>
        <resources>
            <r>http://ccetompkins.org/4-h-youth/activities-events/4-h-youth-fair</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/50924/Stationary_Exhibit_Registration.pdf?1620139270</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/50784/Fair_Book_Revised_2021.pdf?1619622561</r>
            <r>https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.cce.cornell.edu/attachments/45313/2020_Double_Entry_Card_Fillable.pdf?1591723416</r>
        </resources>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Sample evaluation</name>
        <category>Project Evaluations</category>
        <description>Watch the following YouTube to see a sample fair
        project evaluation done between two 4-H members.</description>
        <html>
            <div style="position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 60%;">
                <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kxaF1RuspMY"
                        title="YouTube video player of a Sample 4-H Evaluation"
                        frameborder="0"
                        allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
                        style="position: absolute; left: 0; top: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border: 0;"
                        allowfullscreen="true" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true">
                </iframe>
            </div>
        </html>
        <images>
            <image>Fine Arts A</image>
        </images>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Awards</name>
        <category>Gallery</category>
        <description>Take a moment and reflect on how awesome everyone did this year!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fun at the Fair</name>
        <category>Gallery</category>
        <description>What's a fair without fun?  Send in pictures of
        the fun you have at the fair, complete with a fun caption.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Winning Wednesdays</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <description>WINNING WEDNESDAYS at Texas Roadhouse!  Take a break and
        take out or eat in at Ithaca Texas Roadhouse and they will donate 15%
        of your total check to the 4-H Youth Fair.  When you support Texas
        Roadhouse, they support us!  Just be sure you mention that you support
        4-H to your server.  Winning Wednesdays are July 7, 14 and 21.
        </description>
        <when>July 14, 2021</when>
        <when>July 21, 2021</when>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Fall Festival at Tractor Supply</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <description>Visit 4-H at the Fall Festival at Tractor Supply! 
        Have fun visiting animals, participating in a biggest pumpkin
        contest, and playing fun 4-H games!</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Donations to Tompkins County 4-H</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <description>4-H appreciates any donations.  The donations will
        be used to support the grounds, membership and supply costs, and
        fund more fun activities for youth in the community.  Please
        email Brenda Carpenter (btc6@cornell.edu) for more details on
        who to contact for you to make your donation.</description>
    </activity>
    <activity>
        <name>Chicken BBQ</name>
        <category>Support Us</category>
        <description>The Chicken BBQ is a fundraiser to support the
        grounds, membership and supply costs, and fund more fun
        activities for youth in the community.</description>
    </activity>
</activities>
