<meetings>
    <meeting>
        <month>June</month>
        <day>12,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For our warmup this month, we unscrambled veggies with our bodies.
        We were suprised at everyone's creativity!  One person used sign language,
        another kid held up a pillow to make an I, and two stood hanging a kid
        between them to make an H...  We had a lot of fun!</warmup>
        <html>
            <img src="images/june-12-2020-broccoli.jpg" width="100%"></img>
        </html>
        <summary>
        This month, we learned about growing salad indoors and the different
        beneficial or pest insects.</summary>
        <s>In the Growing Salad Indoors portion of the
        meeting, we learned some general info on various recycled containers, layering
        to improve nutrition, how to prevent bolting and make your lettuce last longer
        and be more productive even in the heat,... And encourage kids to try their own!
        </s>
        <s>
        For the beneficial or pest insect portion of the meeting, we learned about
        some insects in our yard.  For each insect, we learned why they were consedered
        beneficial or a pest, and what we could do to promote or control them.
        For more information, the slideshows can be seen in the Resources page.</s>
        <community-service>We were each encouraged to talk about someone we knew who
        was a front-line worker, and afterwards we drew cards to mail to a hospital
        thanking our essential workers.</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>July</month>
        <day>9,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, we warmed up with a few fun riddles to
        get our brains moving.  Everyone was very creative!  Great job!
        If you would like to see the answers, take a peek at the bottom of this warmup.
        Some of the riddles we used include:</warmup>
        <riddles>
            <r>Which is heavier:  A pound of feathers or a pound of lead?</r>
            <r>Which is faster:  Heat or cold?</r>
            <r>Which American had the biggest family?</r>
        </riddles>
        
        <scavenger-hunt>
        In designing this scavenger hunt, we had to think about ways to allow our members
        to express themselves, be creative and have some fun.  Solving riddles inspires
        us to look at things differently.  It helps us to come up with creative solutions
        and encourage us to 'think outside the box'.  To solve these riddles, we had to
        use our ingenuity and creativity, think critically, and ask ourselves questions
        to discover new solutions.  Everyone brought back some very creative objects for
        the riddles we used!  Here's our scavenger hunt:</scavenger-hunt>

        <s>Something you toss</s>
        <s>Something that changes shape</s>
        <s>Something that smells fantastic</s>
        <s>Something that changes color</s>
        <s>Something you freeze</s>
        <s>Something that grows</s>
        <s>Something shiny</s>
        <s>Something a plant needs</s>
        <s>Something hairy</s>
        <s>Though the stores are closed,
        to only those fearless,
        what can we do,
        to make us not mealless?</s>

        <answers-to-riddles>
        <a>They weigh the same amount!</a>

        <a>Heat, because you can always catch a cold!</a>

        <a>George Washington, because he was the father of our country!</a>
        </answers-to-riddles>

        <summary>This meeting, we had a 4-H Fair update about the scheduled virtual events
        we could participate in, took a look at the data we collected on our favorite insect,
        had a Weed Challenge.  We all did very well!  Good job, everyone!  And finally, we
        had grafted ginkgos during a previous meeting and some were successful!</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we gave updates on
        how our gardens were growing.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the
        awesome work, Botany Besties!</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>August</month>
        <day>14,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, each member finds two objects.  Some of
        these objects included squash, bracelets, a small bottle, and a matrioshki doll
        (Russian nesting doll).  Then, each member takes turns telling
        a few sentences of a story, including both of their objects.  The next
        person then adds to the story with a few more sentences including
        their objects and repeat until everyone has had a turn.  We then read the completed
        story out loud.  We created a story about a bracelet with a secret on how to make a
        potion that made the meany zucchini nice again.  Everyone was very creative!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we had a fun time learning about mimicry and look-a-likes.  We
        learned about identifying characteristics of a plant for identification and learned
        about convergent evolution and evolutionary mimicry.  Then, we did a fun Kahoot to
        review our second weed list and watched the "Vegetable Orchestra" play.</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we gave updates on
        how our gardens were growing.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the
        awesome work, Botany Besties!</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>September</month>
        <day>18,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>We picked veggies from our garden and made art with them.  One member did
        a person, another did a butterfly, and someone even did a Mr. Potatohead!  Afterwards, we
        gave some ideas on how to reuse our veggies after we finished our veggie art.  Two
        members put theirs on a pizza, some just ate them raw (that took care of most of
        the veggies!), and others gave them to their chickens.  Don't worry, we didn't cook
        Mr. Potatohead.  He's reusable veggie art!  Great job, Botany Besties!
        For more examples, see the warmup on the Resources page and take a look at the slideshow
        we used during the meeting.</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we learned about and did a chromatography experiment about Hidden
        Colors on leaves we found around our yard.  Everyone's chromatography turned out wonderful!
        And everyone did amazing on the discussion questions afterwards!  We also did a fun weed
        Kahoot using all of the weeds we've learned so far.  Everyone did great!</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we updated on
        dropping food off for the food pantry and at local Neighborhood Food Hubs to support our
        community.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the awesome work, Botany
        Besties!</community-service>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>October</month>
        <day>23,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <summary>We had a guest speaker present "Plant Breeding 101: How and why humans
        make better crop plants".  We learned why plant breeding is important, how
        it works, and how it impacts all parts of our lives.  We learned the basics of
        artificial selection, a bit of history of crop plants, and had a few interactive
        activities to give us an idea of what plant breeders do and think about.  We were
        so glad to have them present at our meeting!</summary>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>November</month>
        <day>13,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For this meeting's warmup, we had fun with a game similar to Taboo where
        we guessed the different things that could pollinate a plant with the given clues. 
        We learned that there are many more pollinators than just bees.  Feel free to check
        out the slideshow in the warmups in the Resources page!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we had learned about composting with a few guest speakers
        from Cornell.  We learned about what we can compost, how to compost, and a few helper
        critters that help break down our compost into something we can use in out gardens. 
        Also, one of the club members did a fantastic presentation of their favorite Top 5
        Trees!  They taught us about the trees' identifying features, ranges where they grow,
        and their uses.  Their presentation is available in the Topics section on the Resources page.
        For this meeting's science experiment, we learned about the Mysteries of Color.
        We learned how we see colors, how plants see colors, and what we can do to help
        plants grow, using what we learned.  We also played a fun game using color filters to
        review what we learned and reveal secret messages.  The slideshow, along with some other
        learning links, can be found in the Topics section on the Resources page.</summary>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>December</month>
        <day>18,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <plan>We plan to have one of our members teach us about 5 more of their favorite trees. 
        We will make origami pointsettias and snowflakes to give to a local nursing home and
        review what we learned this year by making a fun, end of the year dessert.</plan>
    </meeting>
</meetings>