<meetings>
    <meeting>
        <month>June</month>
        <day>12,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For our warmup this month, we unscrambled words with our bodies.
        I was suprised at everyone's creativity!  One person used sign language,
        another two stood hanging a kid between them to make an H...  We had a
        lot of fun!</warmup>
        <summary>This month, we learned about growing salad indoors and the different
        beneficial or pest insects.  In the Growing Salad Indoors portion of the
        meeting, we learned some general info on various containers, recycled, layering
        to improve nutrition, how to prevent bolting and make you lettuce last longer
        and be more productive even in the heat,... And encouraged kids to try their own!
        And for the beneficial or pest insect portion of the meeting, we learned about
        some insects in our yard.  For each insect, we learned why they were consedered
        beneficial or a pest, and what we could do to promote or control them.</summary>
        <community-service>We were each encouraged to talk about someone we knew who
        was a front-line worker, and afterwards we drew cards to mail to a hospital
        thanking our essential workers.</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>July</month>
        <day>9,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, we went on a scavenger hunt and had fun with a
        few riddles.  Everyone was very creative!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we had a 4-H Fair update about the scheduled virtual events
        we could participate in, took a look at the data we collected on our favorite insect,
        had a Weed Challenge.  We all did very well!  Good job, everyone!  And finally, we
        had grafted ginkgos during a previous meeting and some were successful!</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we gave updates on
        how our gardens were growing.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the
        awesome work, Botany Besties!</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>August</month>
        <day>14,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, we each found two objects and took turns telling
        a few sentences of a story, including both objects.  Everyone was very creative!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we had a fun time learning about mimicry and look-a-likes.  We
        learned about identifying characteristics of a plant for identification and learned
        about convergent evolution and evolutionary mimicry.  Then, we did a fun Kahoot to
        review our second weed list and watched the "Vegetable Orchestra" play.</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we gave updates on
        how our gardens were growing.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the
        awesome work, Botany Besties!</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>September</month>
        <day>18,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, we did some fun veggie art with vegetables we grew.
        One person did a person, another did a butterfly, and someone even did a Mr. Potatohead!
        Great job, Botany Besties!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we learned about and did a chromatography experiment about Hidden
        Colors on leaves we found around our yard.  Everyone's chromatography turned out wonderful!
        And everyone did amazing on the discussion questions afterwards!  We also did a fun weed
        Kahoot using all of the weeds we've learned so far.  Everyone did great!</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we updated on
        dropping food off for the food pantry and at local Neighborhood Food Hubs to support our
        community.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the awesome work, Botany
        Besties!</community-service>
        <images>
            <image>Veggie Art A</image>
            <image>Veggie Art B</image>
            <image>Veggie Art C</image>
        </images>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>October</month>
        <day>9,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <plan>We plan to have a guest speaker present about Plant Breeding.  We may also learn
        about some trees.</plan>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>November</month>
        <day>13,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <plan>We plan to learn about soil and soil improvement, and maybe have a guest speaker talk
        to us about "How to Use a Botanical Key".  We'd love any suggestions!</plan>
    </meeting>
</meetings>