<meetings>
    <meeting>
        <month>June</month>
        <day>12,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For our warmup this month, we unscrambled words with our bodies.
        I was suprised at everyone's creativity!  One person used sign language,
        another two stood hanging a kid between them to make an H...  We had a
        lot of fun!</warmup>
        <summary>This month, we learned about growing salad indoors and the different
        beneficial or pest insects.  In the Growing Salad Indoors portion of the
        meeting, we learned some general info on various containers, recycled, layering
        to improve nutrition, how to prevent bolting and make you lettuce last longer
        and be more productive even in the heat,... And encouraged kids to try their own!
        And for the beneficial or pest insect portion of the meeting, we learned about
        some insects in our yard.  For each insect, we learned why they were consedered
        beneficial or a pest, and what we could do to promote or control them.</summary>
        <community-service>We were each encouraged to talk about someone we knew who
        was a front-line worker, and afterwards we drew cards to mail to a hospital
        thanking our essential workers.</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>July</month>
        <day>9,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <warmup>For the warmup this meeting, we went on a scavenger hunt and had fun with a
        few riddles.  Everyone was very creative!</warmup>
        <summary>This meeting, we had a 4-H Fair update about the scheduled virtual events
        we could participate in, took a look at the data we collected on our favoriteinsect,
        had a Weed Challenge.  We all did very well!  Good job, everyone!  And finally, we
        had grafted ginkgos during a previous meeting and some were successful!</summary>
        <community-service>For this meeting's community service section, we gave updates on
        how our gardens were growing.  Everyone's gardens are doing great!  Keep up the
        awesome work, Botany Besties!</community-service>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>August</month>
        <day>14,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <plan>We plan on having fun discovering Hidden Colors.</plan>
    </meeting>
    <meeting>
        <month>September</month>
        <day>11,</day>
        <year>2020</year>
        <plan>We might do something about soil... Feel free to give suggestions!</plan>
    </meeting>
</meetings>